ANDREW HARRIS

B.Sc. with Honours (Medical Physics)

Enthusiastic workplace safety advocate with Teaching, Management, and Quality Assurance experience and knowledge of ALARA and RP best practices.

STRENGTHS

Persuasive Communication

Management & Mentoring

Research Excellence

Creative Problem Solving and Multi-Tasking

Cooperative Leadership through Extreme Ownership

Devoted to Team Success

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

NATIONAL SHOW SYSTEMS: TECHNICAL DIRECTOR

2011-2024

Organized crew for daily work shifts, supervised Workplace Safety while directing multiple AV departments (Audio, Video, Lighting, Staging) to ensure the successful delivery of a variety of different event types.

TORONTO METRO UNIVERSITY: RESEARCH ASSISTANT 2021-2022

Assisted MSc. students programming in Python with Anaconda for deep learning applications in MRI with COPD patients. Led lab meetings for 10-15 people.

EXPERTISE

Computer Programming

Web Development using Flask, React, SQL

Radiation Protection

"Green Book" Supervisor Safety Training

Aligning Daily Work with SOPs

Teaching and Coaching

Prioritizing Activities in a Fast-Paced Work Environment

CONTACT

Toronto, ON 226-678-5899

Andrew.Haris@torontomu.ca

LinkedIn



EDUCATION

WESTERN UNIVERSITY

2016-2018

P:hD/MCISc Medical Biophysics (incomplete)

- Teaching Assistant: Computer Programming in Python, Statistics for life sciences
- Programming: C++ and the Insight Toolkit (ITK) Medical Imaging toolkit
- Quality Assurance Assistant: LINAC machines in London Regional Cancer Program

RYERSON UNIVERSITY

2011-2016

B.Sc. with Honours (Medical Physics) CGPA 3.87

- Leader in Supported Learning Group program: Physics, Organic Chemistry, Computer Programming in MATLAB, Calculus
- NSERC-USRA grant recipient
- NSERC-Engage grant recipient
- Conducted reading-week review workshops in MATLAB